Hello classmate Truong Ky
Please fill in your information
Hello teacher
MC selection documents
High School TV station
Candidate's full name
Truong Ky
Alright
Which of the following sounds can you express?
All can be done
How many types of things can you do?
If you see it, it's all there
Then you accumulate it all
That's not very good
I see
See which audition suits you best
The king's voice is majestic
We are all at peace
Alright
Okay
Okay, okay
The tyrannical general
What kind of voice is it?
The tyrannical general is
I don't need what you think
I want it my way
Right
The uncle's voice was calm
The uncle was calm
If not comfortable
Then please drink some hot water
Okay
Your high pitch and super boiling water sound
Which one is higher?
Super higher boiling water
"Super Water" wins me over
Right
Probably written like this
Okay
In thirty seconds you can say how many letters or words
Maybe I'm crazy
Got 1 word
Kind of singing a song
Luan
Minh
Nguyet
Great road
Not
Sorry, I was wrong
The brain is not very active now
You can use sound
Do what others can't do?
I
I don't know how bass sounds like this
Can they?
Can you say it?
Seems low
Low sound, huh?
If you introduce yourself with a song
You will choose
"Wukong"
I was young
Heaven fights earth
Alright
Do not worry
It's okay, relax
When the lightning disappeared, the rain stopped
I know you're also waiting for a future
See all spring, summer, fall and winter
That's when I will come to get to know you
Oh girl
Be careful on your side
All night without rest
Get used to change
Never hesitate
Meet surprises every new day
I really tried
Older brother
I want to have you
I have you every hour, every minute
I leaned my cheek against your back
So let's walk around the universe together
Come quickly
Check-in
You have priority, no need to wait
Ticking
You have bought all the time
In this moment
Have fun protecting this universe
Hey, don't go yet
The gift is still in hand
The future is being built
Come inside and sit for a bit
The past has been left behind the door
I thought it was gone but I turned around and realized you were still waiting
I never believed badboys could repent
There was once an eternal heaven and earth
You are mine, I am yours
Destiny is a song
He received the gift with his hands still shaking
Come quickly
Check-in
You have priority, no need to wait
Ticking
I bought all the time
In this moment
I just need to protect this universe
Next, let's challenge you to learn Ly Huong
That is using dance movements
Taking turns taking pictures with three other classmates
You can also ask them to coordinate with you
Okay
Then come on
Whatever I do
I will lean on your shoulder
Okay
Then you can do anything
Just keep being cool
When I count 1 2 3
Come on, prepare
Are you done yet?
Do I need to look at the lens?
It's up to you
Okay
Prepare
1 2 3
Okay, done
What happened just now?
Can I turn my back, like this
Why are you so cold?
Okay, go back
Give me an arm
I won't get hurt, will I?
No
1 2 3
Let me choose the move
You choose the move
I don't want to be passive
Okay, I'll cooperate with you
This is fine
Please put your hands on it
I have to raise one leg
1 2 3
Very good
Thank you four classmates
Shows many talents
Next, we will guess what the video just stopped
What is the next question?
After viewing each excerpt
Listen to my voice command to raise your hand to answer
Correct answer gets 1 point
Come on, let's see
Excerpts from this next challenge
Have you ever seen a rock that floats?
You're joking again
Try this leaf
It's you
Yes, I know
Even the leaves have sunk
Surely the dry leaves will not sink
The reed will not sink, right?
Surely a bunch of reeds will not sink
Surely the shoes won't sink
Even the shoes sank
This is an excerpt from the movie
"Great Saint Sun Wukong Qi Thien"
Everyone can guess what the next sentence is
I no longer feel as excited as before
The real person is here
He even saw it himself
Right, that's why
I guessed it
Okay, Mr. Luong Han Van
Wukong, why did you throw your shoes?
That's the master's
It's possible
He even forgot
Next sentence
It was the year 2000
It's a 2000 movie
Really?
Then there's a little more
But the previous paragraph is correct
The previous paragraph is correct
Yes, there's a little more behind
Why not throw yours
Wukong, why?
Throwing the master's shoes again
Why don't you throw your shoes away?
Take a look at our correct excerpt
Even shoes don't sink
Wukong, why did you even throw your shoes?
Master's down the river
You should throw mine
Is it true?
Right
So this time we add 1 point to Mr. Luong Han Van
Our image of "A Dai Nhi".
If you want to complete it all, you need to complete this game
You must choose your own five senses
Recommended
Then our image of "A Dai Nhi" will be formed
So first we have to see
The five senses of the four friends
He will be made up of his classmates
The following will be shown in turn
The captivating charm of four classmates
First, let's look at our first classmate
So emotional
Every image is there
I find myself ashamed
So handsome
Next let's see
Enjoy the charm of your second classmate
Very wild
The style is hard to hate
You guys look so handsome
Thieu Minh Minh, you have also posed for magazines many times
Please comment a bit
This style is so unique
Are there many flowers in your heart?
Normally look at the face
It's quite arbitrary, isn't it?
Let's invite Mr. Doan Ky
Take a set of photos for a school garden themed magazine
Give me three keywords
The first
Standing attack
Toothache
Supports the waist
I think we will all be forgotten in the end
Can't keep pride, can't keep the past
The mulberry field is always the same
Haven't experienced much impermanence in the world
I will remember your story
Let me forget what I said
Busy traffic, people coming and going
Red flowers and clear wine
Too high
Because the music is too high
How can you blame him?
For me, it will be like that
It's just a little whining about the years
Regret and shortcomings
Always be with me
It's so high
I want to rely on the drizzle to fall on you
Vuong on top of me
Calms the fear and insecurity in my heart
This is the easter egg he prepared
The same goes for long sleepless nights
Can't hide the sadness that fades over time
I can't sing, please sing for me
Ly Van Kiet fighting
Ly Van Kiet is so adorable
Even if you lose your voice, you still sing
Try your best
Your story, I will remember
Forget what I said
Busy traffic, people coming and going
For me, it would be like that
It's just a sigh of regret for a moment
For me, it will be like that again
Regrets and shortcomings are always with me
It seems like a rush of prosperity
Tight intersection
Dancing alone in a cold place
I live on my body
For me, it would be like that
It's just a moment of complaining
As for me, what will happen next?
Regrets and shortcomings are always with me
It seems like a rush of prosperity
Busy intersection
Dancing alone in a cold place
I live on my body
You told me
Next will be our third round
"What business people must know"
Okay
Let's play a warm-up game
First, please close your eyes
Close your eyes
Okay
From number 1 start speaking
This thing
It is
Goosebumps
It's not like I'm a blank vote
If I hold a blank vote, can I say this?
So not sure yet
It's definitely you
Goosebumps
Player number 2
So beautiful
Goosebumps are beautiful
Correct
I'm still pursuing
Very similar to mine
You're not a spy, are you?
That's right you
Art
It's a type of visualization
Are you a blank vote?
Player number 6
What did Mr. Luu Thong say just now?
Art
I feel like it's art
I want to pursue it
That's it, I feel
Except me
Surely everyone will want to
Also really want to pursue
I feel this scene
Doan Ky and Thieu Minh Minh
You can go
Why so
This Minh Minh is so cunning
It's you
Vote
Please vote
6 votes
Goodbye Thieu Minh Minh
I can
Can't talk
Regret "die" guys
I'm off work
No, come back
Now
The game continues
Bonus trophy
High-class
Neither praise nor criticism
Quiet
Player number 5
Glory
What do you think?
I see Doan Ky can go out
What did Doan Ky say?
He's leaning in
Not you
This clearly shows him hugging his big thighs
Someone else just mentioned a reward trophy
The prize trophy is glory
Glory
Obviously you're following me
High-class
I'm like you
Correct
He said so
Now I'm like you
Copy
Ready
Second round of voting
Please vote
What do you mean?
Do you understand how I feel?
Now, the game begins
What
It's not over yet
Do not have
The game continues
There are 2 people
Haven't these two people gone out already?
If the game is not over yet
That means there are still spies
Let's start speaking from Mr. Luu Thong's side
Boiling
This has nothing to do with anything
Older brother
Continue
This round I will
Vote for my brother Luu Thong
Third round of voting
Please prepare
Please raise your hand
4 sao
Circulation
Everyone is in order
One by one they were eliminated
The game continues
Why is starting up so stressful?
Could it be that a spy doesn't know that he is a spy?
Afterward
We
From number 1
Begin
Drama
Stage
Brother, I feel
In this game, we will vote for Mr. Ly Huong
See if you win or lose, okay?
You say one thing
He said once
I said one
I'm afraid you're a "thief"
When other people say I have this
I will see very
Very proud
Same with me, Doan Chinh
If not, I will be impatient
Mr. Doan Chinh, I think we are very similar
Don't quarrel
Get ready
Vote for yourself?
Anyway
Disputes are useless
Congratulations to the civilian team
Won the warm-up competition
Spying is "Ly Huong's dancing technique"
You guess what they are
Acting by Doan Chinh
Answer correctly
Then there was a scene where everyone was talking
Others held blank votes
Thieu Minh Minh
Hold blank ballot
He pointed to everyone here
You have a blank vote
Our third topic
In the game
It's all quite infuriating
Now, topic number 3
Invite free draw
Please show everyone
"Pig teammates"
This side
"Golden Hand Teammate" makes people angrier
So it's definitely the "golden hand opponent" that makes people angrier
I'm really angry and want to give up
Free debate circle
Now
Begin
We see
Definitely a "pig teammate"
Makes people angrier
Correct
Because
Because of that
Now, next
Extremely top
If only I had "pig teammates"
Then I feel like I'm drunk
Then I felt myself
Don't get drunk
Then I won't go
We use our own actions
To prove that "pig teammates" are extremely annoying
When we meet the "golden hand opponent"
We are in trouble
Then we will serve them
Because the opponent is too strong
But when we encounter "pig teammates"
There will be times when you will feel very helpless
You will discover this failure
It has nothing to do with you
Feeling
The greatest human suffering
Comes from
Job
Helpless with yourself
This is the feeling
Brought to us by "Pig Teammates".
Extremely painful
I feel the difference between the two
Comes from
Lose
Because of "pig teammates"
As for yourself, you are not responsible
But because you encounter a "golden hand opponent"
You can only complain that you are not as good as others
What you said is very correct
But he felt it was irrelevant
Because of encountering a "golden hand opponent"
So you will feel very chicken, right?
He encountered a "pig teammate"
Then you will feel that you are okay
So when he encountered "pig teammates"
He will be even angrier
If you encounter a "golden-handed opponent" like Mr. Ho Hai Tuyen
Then I will be angry to death within a moment
Everyone feels
Encountering "pig teammates"
So it's definitely normal
But encountered a "golden hand opponent"
It will be very miserable
Think about it, suddenly there comes a day
Jordan plays basketball with me
So am I angry?
Definitely won't be angry
But what if
You encounter
A group of "pig comrades"
So all the problems
Why "can't sleep"
Why "can't get up"
What "things that should be said"
"Things that shouldn't be said"
You will feel like everything becomes a problem
If there was a day me and Bridge
There's a chance
Playing basketball with Jordan
Jordan was across from us
That's right
He is our "godlike opponent".
We will not be angry
We will feel honored
Honor
But what if
One day Jordan became our teammate
Then Jordan might not be too happy
That's right
I think "teammates are like pigs"
After all
Also our teammates
Is that so?
And
We
Face them
We shouldn't be angry
We should be more tolerant
Who wouldn't say "pig teammate"?
Growing into the person we are today
And facing a "god-like opponent"
Why are we angry?
I think the anger is here
It's not about being angry with your opponent
It's anger at yourself
Angry because you are not as good as others
I think being a teenager
We should
Always move forward
When facing "god-like teammates", always
Full of enthusiasm
Thank you
Facing "god-like teammates"
We can
Whoever is strong doesn't care
I'm still as steady as a rock
Now, please proceed
Make a final argument
I think that when people encounter
Mistakes and failures
So first of all you should
Find the internal cause first
Becomes angrier when facing a "god-like opponent"
Because they are angry with themselves
But it's not
In a situation where there is a "teammate like a pig"
But get angry with your teammates
Need to be tolerant enough
In
The long history of mankind
We will encounter
There will be constant difficulties
We will meet opponents as strong as "gods".
But in this process
When we meet strong people, we will become strong
We won't
Feeling angry
When encountering an opponent as strong as a "god"
Which we should feel excited about
Feel happy
Because we have the opportunity to grow again
But
If we have a "comrade like a pig" by our side.
Then we won't be able to
Through this "pig-like teammate".
Find
Opportunity to grow for yourself
Purpose
Our biggest
It is on the way to overcome difficulties
Never stop growing
That's right
Vote
Next up, inference lovers
Which team will you vote for in the end?
Please see the big screen
Come on up
Clap for everyone
First question
Will test your ability to come up with the right song
When listening to different stories from the audience
First context
We would like to invite audience Khai Khai to propose a topic
Come on, Khai Khai
In the karaoke room
I want to be in front of my classmates that I secretly love
Show it off really well
So how should I sing the song?
Tomorrow I will marry you
Very direct, right?
Yes, very good
I also thought of it
Now, let's do a little show
Yes
I'm on the left
He's close to the right, first photo
Don't dare be too intimate
Belongs to the two of us
The face is too innocent
It's three people now
One person lives, two people are shy, three people go out together
I'll come back here for you
Come on, Mr. Ky
I can't forget you
Don't go to the horizon or the sea
Just stay by my side
If so
Yes
Next here
In the next situation, who will be the one to bring it up?
Roommate borrowed money
But still refused to pay
So what song should I choose to remind him?
I really want to borrow another 500 dong
I figured it out
Do you still remember?
That red hot summer
I see it's your wallet
Can really comfort my wound
I have a post
It's Cantonese music
Cantonese
Very simple, very direct, very on topic
Money money money
That's okay
Straight to the topic, great
Classic song
I came up with another song
I want, I want you
I want you
Mr. Ky, so your answer is
Congratulations brilliantly
Congratulations on your fortune
I want to return the money
No one is afraid of polite people
Yes, no one is afraid of polite people
Yes, very good
Well, third situation
My boss calls me continuously every weekend
I want to share a song with my friends
To refer to him
How to hint to your boss
Don't contact me on the weekend
I thought of it, here's the article
It's true that he is evil
Likes to use innocent eyes
I lied a few times but I thought it was true
Okay
I came up with a great song
Tomorrow he won't go to work anymore
So happy, the top of the top
Be as lazy as you want to be
This is a certain regional accent
Chengdu
The background sounds like a Ha Nam accent
So that's really cool
There is a song that is very suitable
If it's to hint at the boss
Don't bother me this weekend
Now is my time
Don't go to work on weekends
Very suitable
The song "I want to have fun" is fine
I want to have fun
I want to sleep peacefully
That's right, sleep peacefully
Okay, this phrase is extremely accurate
So now
We start the voting round
In 5 seconds
In the songs introduced
Which article suits your opinion best?
Come on, three two one
Please hold up the board
Au Duong Tinh received all the votes
Because he chose the song "Call me by Fire"
Right
That's right
It's truly top notch
Yes, everyone
Next, I would like to introduce to everyone
Game rules of this round
This round is called "This turn I play"
Each team will have 5 cards in hand
Only play 2 to 3 cards at a time
And the corresponding relationship must be stated
Other teams can vote to decide whether to pass or not
If not approved, the card will have to be withdrawn
And must add 1 more leaf
The team that gets all the cards is the winner
The reason for each issue cannot be the same
The real story or information needs to be told
Only counted as valid
Yes
Please everyone read the article
Confirm the cards in hand
That's okay too
Look behind you
Leave it here already
Ok
Do you know how to read the article?
This
These cards are hardly related
They are all leaves that are not in the same world
Let's see how people explain it
And do others accept it?
Ok
This is so difficult
This is quite difficult, you have to put it all together
Put it in the hardest game
Which leaf is the most difficult?
This
This can be a substitute for anyone
Any
Pull hammer and paper
Goodbye
Good
Hoa Thu attacked first
Then we will produce these 3 cards
Doraemon, happy sheep and Ultraman
The relationship between them is non-human
I have an opinion
Doesn't Ultraman have a live actor?
No, we are talking about the character Ultraman
Not its actors, right?
Before Ultraman transformed, he was still human
It's not
Wait, everyone wait
Could it be that before the transformation, it didn't look like this?
It doesn't look like this
Doesn't look like that
Normally he has a different appearance, not like this
Normally he has a different appearance
So what does he normally look like?
When you're normal, you're a normal person
Looks like a normal person
Ok
I would like to confirm again
Everyone wants to draw their own cards, right?
Not
You guys go vote, okay?
Because there's only one team that has an opinion
That's right, if there's still a team that has an opinion
Then they will have to withdraw their cards
Everyone should first build support for each other
To avoid that, we also raised questions
I support Mr. Hai Tuyen
Neither are human
Isn't that right?
Yes, then this team is the most important
Is it human? Please tell me
Do you and Mr. Hai Tuyen have any conflicts with each other?
Do not have
Well then we have no comments at all
Yes, if so then pass
He didn't know Ultraman was once that person
That's it, just don't make people take back the song
Even ruined the relationship with a team
It will be difficult for us to release the cards later
Yes, next will be Minh Minh's team
That's it, we lost forever
Then was then, now is now
Don't create relationships like that
We are all vindictive people
Come on, 3 cards
Luffy, Na Tra and Little Fox
Is that right?
We can pick it up and read it
Alright
First of all, there are three people in this group
They're all wearing tank tops
Na Tra wears overalls
Is Luffy wearing a tank top?
Okay, you said I said
Besides that
All of their pants are blue
The shirts are all red
No, on this side there is a person wearing green underwear
Correct
Several people immediately
Okay, so let's switch
I'm afraid this won't make it through
Do you have any other reason?
I already had the first reason earlier
First, so except this one
Most of them
all wear red shirts
and blue pants
Thieu Minh Minh, you know
Actually, he just said a more general idea
We cannot refute
The more details you say, the more disadvantageous it will be for you
All are men
It's so great
I would like to ask if the other 3 teams have any opinions
On Apr
In "Journey to the West" 1986 version
The performer is a girl
But she plays a male role
Powerless to refute
Correct
Okay, are you sure?
No comments
Okay, card issued successfully
Indeed, it is male
Okay, pass
Van Thao and Ngao Khuyen, please invite your team to play
We think these 3 panels
All possess the ability to maintain space
far beyond the level of ordinary people
What is emptiness?
It's time stopped in the air
Sakuragi is
Jump very high
These two are both very long
Yes, Sakuragi's forte is dunks
Correct
I see no comments
You don't have an opinion, do you?
What about you?
That's OK
Then the two of you passed away
Okay, then it's passed
Okay, next is Brige and Bo Tap Tinh
I'm thinking of something more unusual
You say it
Any
Naruto, Sun Wukong and Conan
They are all in some situations
can become larger
Yes, this makes sense
Yes, everything will change big
Is Sun Wukong okay?
Sun Wukong's Nhu Y Stick can grow bigger
So Sun Wukong himself can become very big
I can think of something more unusual
Okay, you say it
Naruto is a Fire Shadow (Naruto story)
Conan was once made into a movie
Sun Wukong from Shanghai My Photo (studio name)
All are "Photos"
It's all "Photos"
Leave
Cut that part out
Let's just take the big one
I can see it
Okay, okay
Through
How about you guys?
We have no opinion
Now let's return to this place
We have a function card
A Dai Nhi card
It's from Marvel
It is Iron Man
They are in "Avengers 4"
are all dead
Is this a direct win?
Okay, successful posting
So we assign him an additional card
Very good
This time, I committed a crime and died
Holding grudges will always kill you, right?
In the next round, two people will be given cards
Black Cat Sheriff, Pikachu
Yes, what are they all?
No hair at all
Pikachu and the Black Cat sheriff
There is hair all over the body
Yes, the whole body has hair
It's fur
Pikachu has fur
I once watched "Detective Pikachu"
Correct
In the movie, there is hair
I feel most important
There's no proof that he said it had no hair
Because I've never seen it before
Sheriff Black Cat doesn't wear a hat
What if he took off his hat?
What if the back is all hair, right?
Yes, please vote
If you have a different opinion with this team, please raise your hand
Let's raise it together, quickly
Now, at the same time, you must
one more plate
It's hard to differentiate
What do you guys want?
We thought okay, okay
We are nothing
Issue a card or take a card
They all come from abroad
I feel it's too superficial
We thought of a better answer earlier
They all have super powers
It doesn't have superpowers, it just relies on technique
Yes, I doubt it
Come on, guys
If in doubt, please raise your hand
Suspect
Okay, collect the card
We got a card that's not easy to get out
No problem
You can try it all at once
The 2 pictures appear to be...
Come on, let's take a look
Who is that?
Bao Thanh Thien
Kaifeng has Bao Thanh Thien
How come?
Now you two decide on a reason
Then let the remaining three teams proceed to differentiate
The three of them all have catchphrases
What is it?
Come on, say something
Bao Thanh Thien
Open the knife
That's right
What about Sheriff Black Cat
Black Cat, surely you know
You don't know Sheriff Black Cat?
I said Pikachu first
Pikachu, pikachu
This is over
Mainly the Black Cat sheriff
Okay, everyone vote
Come on, 3 2 1 invite doubt
If so
They'll have to draw one more card, right?
Can't get out
Next is Bo Tap Tinh
Come on, let's play the card we can't argue with
Yes, we have one
Bighead
A Dai Nhi
We, Big Head, can change it however we want
This is Little Head's father
In the cartoon, they are father and son
Or I can also transform this card
become a robot cat
Them and Big Head
The head is larger than the body
Yes, so these two are not a problem
Not wrong
Okay
Congratulations to Brige and Bo Tap Tinh on their victory
Congratulations guys
So your team
Bet on the next official game
You can decide the order of posting
OK
Let everyone check out Mr. Ho Hai Tuyen's article
We have already thought of it
Before they made their move
Everyone will read their moves once first
Yes, very good
Hoang Phi Hong will speak
Foshan has no shadow
Balala the Fairies, let's put on a little show
Balala's power surged, the black demon transformed
Alright
In this program
I used force to defeat Trieu Van Trac
I just like people like you
Oh my God
Being able to meet you here is not easy
Mr. Luu Thong contacted Mr. Trieu Van Trac
What kind of person do you think Trieu Van Trac is?
How is it, it's him
Why did you drop your pen, brother?
So scared
Is it really that scary?
Not scary, extremely adorable
Force is only against outsiders
We're still pretty safe
Force is used against other teams
Is the atmosphere very strong?
Eye contact with him probably didn't last more than 10 seconds
I feel 2 seconds
3 seconds away
Not the big bay's big brother
Quite a big deal, wearing clothes like this
Quite big
Wear clothes like this
I know
We are
On the left is GAI
In the middle is Mr. Trieu Van Trac
Trieu Van Trac
On the right is Cao Han Vu
Congratulations on your correct answer
Now, let's show everyone the original photo
Mr. Trieu Van Trac feels very righteous
That's right, we also remind you for a moment
These are the photos
This is a photo from many years ago
That's why there are people at the airport not wearing masks
Don't pay attention, everyone
Please let me know if you think this is appropriate
Which brother should I give the most to?
in "The brother who overcomes all obstacles"?
This is a gift
Mr. Trieu Van Trac left
Why did you give it to Trieu Van Trac?
Trieu Van Trac needs it
You got me
There will be no more loss of direction
I couldn't understand any words
I guess one
3 2 1, come on
Mr. Au Duong Tinh
Very soon it will be
can handle it
Is this Mr. Trieu Van Trac?
That person on the left
It will be resolved very quickly
Can handle it
It must be resolved very quickly
Just now you roughly translated the meaning
Then we'll take a look
Anyone else know the radio from just now?
What did you say just now?
Can you listen to it again?
Okay, let's listen again
Turn the sound up a bit
I know the last sentence is "I confirm"
"I rushed out early in the morning"
The last sentence is correct
So what about the previous sentence, the previous sentence
I guess
The first two sentences are probably
"They are very smart"
"After eating the meat pie, I rushed out early in the morning."
Meat pie is the focus
Meat pie
Extremely unique
But not the correct answer
Very smart
I know
Come on, Mr. Lam Hieu Phong
"The two of them are outstanding"
"I just called them, they rushed out"
Thank you Mr. Lam Hieu Phong
But that was not the correct answer
Or should I say the first sentence and the last sentence?
for you guys
Then we guess the sentence in the middle
Is it possible?
Okay
The previous sentence is "Teacher Lieu really did it a few times"
What is "how many times"?
Just now, Au Duong Tinh was able to answer
That last sentence
"I rushed out early in the morning"
Yes, "rushed out early in the morning"
Let's look at the sentence in the middle
"Teacher Lieu really did it a few times"
(Guess together) "Going out early in the morning"
Now I doubt it is
Trieu Van Trac is talking nonsense
The second sentence is
Or just imitate it directly
I know
Mr. Lam Hieu Phong
"Teacher Lieu really did it a few times"
It's a bit similar
Right
Mr. Ta Thien Hoa
"Teacher Lieu really did it a few times"
"He finished it very quickly"
"I went out early in the morning"
This topic can be a bit difficult
Or should I announce the correct answer?
No one gets points for this question
Just now, Mr. Trieu Van Trac said:
"Teacher Lieu really did it a few times"
"I recovered my sight very quickly"
"I went out early in the morning"
Visual recovery?
Yes, this is really difficult
I've heard it many times and still don't understand
It's true it's not simple